that let's go to Pratima a few days ago but I have done it
quickly
hello hello Shyam Pratima fuel must learn to I
found Tan Graduation in built SIM
activated a patient United University
President President and Yantra and
Sindoor is diet Chainpur famous place these
days is the name Giri ok very good and very good I like this that I want to see
my same pattern definition
of higher level reported in the very good
care friends very good very good
tell me which topic is
social networking let's first talk about social
networking sites and social networking and
social networking sites gives very very
nice computer networking site question on
phone number one by using social networking
sites very good but I can give the sharing
of knowledge and information social networking
sites this relationship with no appeal to the
government officer social networking site
Twitter social media and social media on
Wednesday s
quid ihar-udhar food extent they must be very easy
cyber bullying entries changer have below New Delhi
Increased serious they celebrate angels
places you can by doing social networking
sites like you very-very miss you want to
speak on social networking sites on hello hello
sandhya organized diseases is your
body's topic isn't it direct interview is
n't it now
my dear will there be voice messages
I had given you social networking material no
problem in your affair
send me clippings in a day or two and
I will check all of them make
good ones send me explanations also I am
not getting response from Sneha but
this one in lifting a
wife in or your voice is not coming you
mute unmute
so come on Dhaniya that's all that too no problem let's give
our back Chandni
Pratima you will speak on this topic next
I will say well done Kavita you are
also connected right ok you and we have
direct interviews of Pratiksha who is from Bhilwara city her
assistant manager is yours so you prepare the
role of teacher and sent it to me
Now after this class, I will not but make the
role of a teacher, that is, give a
little longer answer of the profile for two-three minutes,
okay,
I will make it as you want, okay, let's
say Pratima, say well done on the topic, so
that generalization corporation loot-loot general general general general
international area in general and
images of the day
that their inverter competitive advantages
computer advantages of firms and which one is very
good for producing quality
products in general and only one general
competition in English, the
questions were objective, general election
special edition Champcash will be world
class subject and hi special item my
share something very next topic padh lo
mention in mathematics UIDAI UIDAI goes Aadhar
card, say it is
unit, it means
mention in unit 124 issues of sexual frustrations in
English for government jobs in India
for every minute and responsible for
implementing the ideals, Chairman of Planning Commission
of India and Vice Chairman
Authority of India in June 2017 Delhi
Technical  University Udaipur 19 number hai
a stranger na sonu nigam first lady [ __ ] after
dark night by manmohan singh
slogan slogan in aam aadmi ka aadhar number
only for information of government of
india and government subsidy in creative
manch creative manch
MP3 dimaag aap aadhar card information in
people information in english and your
privacy 217 information in 2018 supreme
court mission laga jaata hai not mandatory
for element confusion it is for every indian is very
good system for eliminating
vision and mission culture of commission question
from indian it will also will tell you are you get the
amount directly from the bank
account it will also help for eliminating
the illegal migrants and anti-national
activities and control bhi question
english mention in proper hai nayyar thank
you very good topics you have covered a lot in
confusion of would like to say that then your
topic was started let's go for topic
digitization you have top
prithvi a station of  Banking sector properly a
little admission in numbers continue in
digital from this man mere
ko worker provider Tata company ne do
din kal ekkthi customer hai
10 customer easily dera account anytime
listed this is why that time and expenses are
9 2012 free transaction Amazon cashless
transaction increase the money transaction
answer is the information reduce
unemployment problem for villagers and don't know how do you do
online transaction
only know about security for
[music] everything everything in this
question I don't like him life is our
country in the security and IT will be very good very very
good benefits will be milega
and now the last topic this is looking very good
Shubhendu arre good hard work na chahiye nahi boliye
Pratima saath aa I
ignore changing face of education sas
ambulance for teaching and learning
technology development and basic rules of
tooth technologies SIM use party and
society and enough power  to do it is the what
is the rustampur the loop technology to
support any channel or
leaves knowledge to powerful tool to have a
intercourse to and transfer education technology
designs and in the relationship between teacher
and student and technology cold and fog
the teaching and learning more meaningful
students of vibrant hair to long with
students through the technological application
benefits of intent on next day and
night in easy way two wheeler location skill the
meaning of rose day students of the year
title for
that tata agile need in one place and can
learn for its campaign difficulties and
disadvantages and student student of the
india will bluetooth on
a standing where is chapter bahut kaise laga
result priya would like to speak on any topic
yes yes speak on technology
what is the matter now
jhala ji continue to change the face of
education with the help of technology can
communicate rose life from all over the
world in the
next flight co labs for helping
tour of england  Spoon lemon juice Lemon is used as fuel for
Ajay
that and disadvantage of
that take the disadvantage of everything like if
you make science your servant you can easily
and if you make it a master then there will be ₹10
problem in science so good servant but
master fiction and what Pratima had told
that there are many students from different districts
and the screens are ours,
oh right way
I am very good very very and
that I want you to tell me something about SSC
Bank what do you know tell me I have understood it well
[Music]
that Ramesh Chandra Das obscene book main branch
in Vadodara Gujarat and cooperative office in
Mumbai Maharashtra SSC Bank Sangh
president Naresh Kumar Pundir and 500 to 1000
years she was very good very good it
disappears in between and did
n't you hear the topic of sugar well
hello Sandhya our tool is to search you for
network issues and network is not working well
today our it's new  Voice
modulation is coming
let's talk to our Supriya
how is our old is gold Supriya how is
this facility also Supriya can you
flatten the work of Swiss Banker a little bit can you
student love you to you anishth
gym and simple simple wonderland
play commercial bank red dhir wwe result
injection okay so you do one thing, I will
tell you the method, make two questions, make one for
me without ghee
what is future banker program and make one of fusion
band
what are the qualities required to enter the program so that
we can make two good questions
Sneha is my voice coming bhaiya
tanha you waiting for your voice is
that such laughter visibility is coming
yes it is gone now is my voice going or not
you
hello hello Shyam my voice is going
well would you like to say two lines on any
topic judi ke ki
119 yes social networking and yes
tell me what is the matter
my tab Kumar and social networking and
change your  Life ok ok ok
playlist of social work very good yes
that social networking
half of the social networking sites with zero
balance there people agreed a
dil ki baat ankhon se man ki baat no Modi
ji it's all with social networking and there is any more I want to
address in the yes
that your and disadvantage of turn on the
fruit of the scientist I am not ready yet no
problem you have not received it no
problem see you guys learn this
from Pratima that Pratima has prepared all the topics
now you have to wear a dress in which
Pratima is at least 10 kilometers ahead of you guys
now you guys at least
start jogging so that you will reach something per month
why Priya Rani yes you
sent me that clipping what a GD topic
that how many birds have you sent one lady how many fears have you sent
here is one minute less yes it is
less you speak at least 2 minutes on one topic
okay and take my
Telegram Telegram group Telegram ID
video classes otherwise I will check on that I would
like to tell you Pratima  Please
send me all the topics even Suprita's
interview preparation is very good Sukriti
that you will make it on what is Future Venture Program
and qualities many thoughts to become an anchor
that this is the name of the program isn't it Future
Venture Program that's why it is not yes anyone can make it
on this program as you
said, it is good to make it by making someone else better so
now listen to me listen you all three Priya and
Pratima listen carefully my
voice is coming till now I want to
see you all three fighting in the next round
come to the topics now
tell me on which topic will you fight tomorrow
tell me no that's it Sneha who has gone,
most of the companies have prepared for her these days
give Sneha a chance laptops from the wards
so okay Sonia tomorrow's timing will be the same
and you guys will fight on this topic for half an
hour 30 minutes then the question ok
Pratima dowry percentage of the game will be because it is 10
kilometers ahead from you guys yes absolutely
absolutely fine right I take your best wishes
you guys don't stop practicing  Amazing
practice, I take interviews even in 1984,
whoever among you is interested, please let me know, is it
okay?